Guide to the Asian CineVision Records TAM.416
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Video Recordings
  - Video 638: CCTV labeled "Emergency," which served as a backup broadcast tape for CCTV, cuid1901 (Box 133, U-matic 638)
  - Video 639: "'Freckled Rice' and sample logo", cuid1902 (Box 133, U-matic 639)
    Duration: 10 minutes
  - Video 640: "New Jail in Chinatown" CCTV Production, cuid1903 (Box 133, U-matic Video 640)
    Duration: 23 minutes
  - Video 641: CCTV labeled "Peter's Movie at Hong Kong", cuid1904 (Box 133, U-matic 641)
    The first half of the video is silent.
  - Video 642: CCTV labeled "Raw footage 1/28/85", January 28, 1985; cuid1905 (Box 133, U-matic 642)
    Duration: 35 minutes
  - Video 643: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "TV Commercial Master", cuid1906 (Box 134)
  - Video 644: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "Workshop Final Edit", cuid1907 (Box 134)
  - Video 645: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "'The Young Concubine' sample reel", cuid1908 (Box 134)
  - Video 646: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "'The Young Concubine' sample reel", cuid1909 (Box 134)
  - Video 647: Unidentified, cuid1910 (Box 134)
  - Video 648: Unidentified, cuid1911 (Box 134)
  - Video 649: Unidentified, cuid1912 (Box 134)
  - Video 650: Unidentified, cuid1913 (Box 134)
  - Video 651: Unidentified, cuid1914 (Box 134)
  - Video 652: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1979, 2nd, "Same Difference," "Lion Dance," "Odyssey For Peace," CCTV labeled "0B6", cuid1915 (Box 135)
  - Video 653: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1983, 6th, Toshio Matsumoto films: "Connection" (1981), "Relation" (1982), "Shift" (1982), CCTV labeled "0B10", cuid1916 (Box 135)
  - Video 654: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1983, 6th, Films: "Fool's Dance," "So Far From India,," "James Wong Howe," "The Silence," "Spirit of the Dream House," "Playland," "The Beginning," "Hong Kong Dong," The Last Game," "Matrimony, cuid1917 (Box 135)
  - Video 655: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1985, 8th, press conference, camera 1, cuid1918 (Box 135)
  - Video 656: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1985, 8th, press conference, camera 2, cuid1919 (Box 135)
  - Video 657: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, press conference, CCTV labeled "B71", cuid1920 (Box 135)
  - Video 658: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, Silver Palace, CCTV labeled "B74", cuid1921 (Box 135)
  - Video 659: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, Rosemary speakers, CCTV labeled "B72", cuid1922 (Box 135)
  - Video 660: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 1, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B73", cuid1923 (Box 135)
  - Video 661: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 2, speakers, CCTV labeled "B75", cuid1924 (Box 135)
  - Video 662: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 3, speakers, CCTV labeled "B76", cuid1925 (Box 135)
  - Video 663: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 4, speakers, CCTV labeled "B77", cuid1926 (Box 135)
  - Video 664: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 5, speakers, CCTV labeled "B78", cuid1927 (Box 135)
  - Video 665: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1986, 9th, day 5, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B79", cuid1928 (Box 135)
  - Video 666: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, Opening night, tape 1, cuid1929 (Box 135)
  - Video 667: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 2, day 3, day 4, cuid1930 (Box 135)
  - Video 668: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 5, cuid1931 (Box 135)
  - Video 669: Asian American International Film Festival (AAIFF), 1987, 10th, day 5, cuid1932 (Box 135)
  - Video 670: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF) Stan Egi, cuid1933 (Box 135)
  - Video 671: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 1, Private Eyes, CCTV labeled "B64", cuid1934 (Box 135)
  - Video 672: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 2, Millennium, CCTV labeled "B65", cuid1935 (Box 135)
  - Video 673: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 3, Millennium, CCTV labeled "B66", cuid1936 (Box 135)
  - Video 674: Asian American International Video Festival (AAIVF), 4th, day 3, Millennium, portable camera, CCTV labeled "B67", cuid1937 (Box 135)
  - Video 675: Asian Film Series opening, cuid1938 (Box 135)
  - Video 676: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion: China, 12/14/86, tape 1, cuid1939 (Box 135)
  - Video 677: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion: Japan, 12/14/86, tape 2, cuid1940 (Box 135)
  - Video 678: Asian Film Series, 1986, Panel Discussion, 12/14/86, tape 3, cuid1941 (Box 135)
  - Video 679: FFF, 1985, Day 1, Opening, 11/22/85, CCTV labeled "B61", cuid1942 (Box 135)
  - Video 680: FFF, 1985, Panel Discussion 1, 11/24/85, CCTV labeled "B62", cuid1943 (Box 135)
  - Video 681: FFF, 1985, Panel Discussion 2, 11/24/85, CCTV labeled "B63", cuid1944 (Box 135)
  - Video 682: Press Con., CCTV labeled "B23", cuid1945 (Box 135)
  - Video 683: Press Conference 1987, cuid1946 (Box 135)
  - Video 684: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1947 (Box 135)
  - Video 685: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1948 (Box 135)
  - Video 686: Asian American Heritage Festival, cuid1949 (Box 135)
  - Video 687: Asian American Heritage Festival, hand held camera, tape 1, cuid1950 (Box 135)
  - Video 688: Asian American Heritage Festival, hand held camera, tape 2, cuid1951 (Box 135)
  - Video 689: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 2, cuid1952 (Box 135)
  - Video 690: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 4, cuid1953 (Box 135)
  - Video 691: Asian American Heritage Festival, left camera, tape 5, cuid1954 (Box 135)
  - Video 692: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 1, cuid1955 (Box 135)
  - Video 693: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 3, folk singer, cuid1956 (Box 135)
  - Video 694: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 4, cuid1957 (Box 135)
  - Video 695: Asian American Heritage Festival, right camera, tape 6, cuid1958 (Box 135)
  - Video 696: Cultural Festival, CCTV labeled "B056", cuid1959 (Box 136, Betamax Video 696)
  - Video 697: Philippines Cinema, CCTV labeled "0B24", cuid1960 (Box 136, Betamax Video 697)
  - Video 698: AAMHC, Panel 2, 5/2/81, CCTV labeled "B045", cuid1961 (Box 136, Betamax Video 698)
  - Video 699: AAMHC, Panel 3: Russell Baba, Tape II Children's song,, CCTV labeled "B043", cuid1962 (Box 136, Betamax Video 699)
  - Video 700: AAMHC, Panel 5, 5/3/81, CCTV labeled "B050", cuid1963 (Box 136, Betamax Video 700)
  - Video 701: AAMHC, Panel 5 and Fini, 5/3/81, CCTV labeled "B044", cuid1964 (Box 136, Betamax Video 701)
  - Video 702: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 1 (stationary camera), cuid1965 (Box 136, Betamax Video 702)
  - Video 703: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 2 (stationary camera), cuid1966 (Box 136, Betamax Video 703)
  - Video 704: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape 3 (stationary camera), interview, cuid1967 (Box 136, Betamax Video 704)
  - Video 705: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape A (sideline), cuid1968 (Box 136, Betamax Video 705)
  - Video 706: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape B (sideline), cuid1969 (Box 136, Betamax Video 706)
  - Video 707: Asian American Women Speak Out, 3/31/85, Tape C (handheld), cuid1970 (Box 136, Betamax Video 707)
  - Video 708: Asian Women United/Makasako, Rough Cut #1 -51 min., cuid1971 (Box 136, Betamax Video 708)
  - Video 709: Aquino Memorial Service, Interview, 8/26/83, cuid1972 (Box 136, Betamax Video 709)
  - Video 710: Asian American Arts II, Corky and Gene, Interview Part 2, Still photos, cuid1973 (Box 136, Betamax Video 710)
  - Video 711: CCTV Clothing Demo, CCTV labeled "B128", cuid1974 (Box 136, Betamax Video 711)
  - Video 712: Chinese Exodus From Vietnam II, CCTV labeled "B022", cuid1975 (Box 136, Betamax Video 712)
  - Video 713: Cultural Benefit for Hiroshima Victims, CCTV labeled "B151", cuid1976 (Box 136, Betamax Video 713)
  - Video 714: CCTV Doctor Yang, CCTV labeled "B67", cuid1977 (Box 136, Betamax Video 714)
  - Video 715: Journey Through New York Chinatown (complete program) (for Nancy Tong), cuid1978 (Box 136, Betamax Video 715)
  - Video 716: Vincent Chin Memorial, CCTV labeled "B157", cuid1979 (Box 136, Betamax Video 716)
  - Video 717: Wayne Wang Dim Sum Press Conference, 7/18/85, cuid1980 (Box 136, Betamax Video 717)
  - Video 718: P.A.L.M. Tagbilaran Religious Day Feast, 5/6/84, tape 1, cuid1981 (Box 136, Betamax Video 718)
  - Video 719: P.A.L.M. Tagbilaran Religious Day Feast, 5/6/84, tape 2, cuid1982 (Box 136, Betamax Video 719)
  - Video 720: P.A.L.M. presents: Filipino Writers in Exile: Basement workshop reading/ 17 April 1984, Faigao, Francia, Florentine, Rosca, cuid1983 (Box 136, Betamax Video 720)
  - Video 721: Disarmament tape, CCTV labeled "B003", cuid1984 (Box 136, Betamax Video 721)
  - Video 722: Japanese American hearings: San Francisco Commission on Wartime Relocation, CCTV labeled "B049", cuid1985 (Box 136, Betamax Video 722)
  - Video 723: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment, CCTV labeled "B59", cuid1986 (Box 136, Betamax Video 723)
  - Video 724: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment interview, CCTV labeled "B70", cuid1987 (Box 136, Betamax Video 724)
  - Video 725: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment investigation, cuid1988 (Box 136, Betamax Video 725)
  - Video 726: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment investigation, cuid1989 (Box 136, Betamax Video 726)
  - Video 727: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment press conference, CCTV labeled "B128", cuid1990 (Box 136, Betamax Video 727)
  - Video 728: Redress and reparations for Japanese internment reception, cuid1991 (Box 136, Betamax Video 728)
  - Video 729: Stereotypes, CCTV labeled "B023", cuid1992 (Box 136, Betamax Video 729)
  - Video 730: Stereotype excerpt "Pearls," CCTV labeled "B002", cuid1993 (Box 136, Betamax Video 730)
  - Video 731: Stereotypes in the Media: TV excerpts, CCTV labeled "B024", cuid1994 (Box 136, Betamax Video 731)
  - Video 732: Stereotypes in the Media: Commission against Fort Apache demonstration, CCTV labeled "B040", cuid1995 (Box 136, Betamax Video 732)
  - Video 733: Stereotypes in the Media: Charlie Chan demonstration, CCTV labeled "B041", cuid1996 (Box 136, Betamax Video 733)
  - Video 734: Charlie Chan demonstration, CCTV labeled "B042", cuid1997 (Box 136, Betamax Video 734)
  - Video 735: ACV Philippino Interview, CCTV labeled "B34", cuid1998 (Box 136, Betamax Video 735)
  - Video 736: Korean-Am interview, cuid1999 (Box 136, Betamax Video 736)
  - Video 737: Jessica's Performance, CCTV labeled "B106", cuid2000 (Box 136, Betamax Video 737)
  - Video 738: Group 3, second project: Radio DJ, cuid2001 (Box 136, Betamax Video 738)
  - Video 739: Group I, Project II, tape II: Performance (Marlena), cuid2002 (Box 136, Betamax Video 739)
  - Video 740: Mr. Carter, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B038", cuid2003 (Box 137, Betamax Video 740)
  - Video 741: Mr. Carter, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B039", cuid2004 (Box 137, Betamax Video 741)
  - Video 742: Mrs. Carter #1, CCTV labeled "B035", cuid2005 (Box 137, Betamax Video 742)
  - Video 743: Mrs. Carter #2, CCTV labeled "B036", cuid2006 (Box 137, Betamax Video 743)
  - Video 744: Ezra Vogel interview: "Japan as number 1," camera #1, Rene Tajima, 11/12, CCTV labeled "B118", cuid2007 (Box 137, Betamax Video 744)
  - Video 745: Ezra Vogel interview: "Japan as number 1," camera #2, Rene Tajima, 11/12, CCTV labeled "B103", cuid2008 (Box 137, Betamax Video 745)
  - Video 746: Demonstrations in New York for and against Chiang's Presidency in Taiwan, 5/20/78, CCTV labeled "B030", cuid2009 (Box 137, Betamax Video 746)
  - Video 747: Presentation(?), cuid2010 (Box 137, Betamax Video 747)
  - Video 748: Boycott Year of the Dragon, 8/16/85, cuid2011 (Box 137, Betamax Video 748)
  - Video 749: Asian American Experience: Senior Center Building (12/15), Alan Cohen (1-185), Aleutian Woman (185-800), CCTV labeled "B22, cuid2012 (Box 137, Betamax Video 749)
  - Video 750: Mutya Gener, K.C.K., CCTV labeled "B10", cuid2013 (Box 137, Betamax Video 750)
  - Video 751: Support for US-China Diplomatic Normalization, CCTV labeled "B032", January 1, 1979; cuid2014 (Box 137, Betamax Video 751)
    Duration: 31 minutes
    This recording includes footage of a march and a rally on the day that the United States and China normalized diplomatic relations. Speakers, including Esther Gollobin and Susan Warren, address a large crowd. A march celebrating the day is shown, as well as footage of a counter-protest.
  - Video 752: Against US-China Diplomatic Normalization, CCTV labeled "B031", January 1, 1979; cuid2015 (Box 137, Betamax Video 752)
    Duration: 49 minutes
    This recording includes footage of a march and a rally on the day that the United States and China normalized diplomatic relations. Pro-Taiwan counter-protesters are shown chanting, singing, and being interviewed by CCTV reporters.
  - Video 753: F.O.B. by David Henry Hwang, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B037", cuid2016 (Box 137, Betamax Video 753)
  - Video 754: F.O.B. by David Henry Hwang, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B034", cuid2017 (Box 137, Betamax Video 754)
  - Video 755: Sun Rise play, CCTV labeled "B29", cuid2018 (Box 137, Betamax Video 755)
  - Video 756: Mako, lead actor from Hito Hata: Raise the Banner, CCTV labeled "B28", cuid2019 (Box 137, Betamax Video 756)
  - Video 757: Mako and Hito Hata Interview, 3/28/81, CCTV labeled "B39", cuid2020 (Box 137, Betamax Video 757)
  - Video 758: Roman Tam and Michelle Yim at the Tropicana, Christmas 1982, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B047", cuid2021 (Box 137, Betamax Video 758)
  - Video 759: Roman Tam and Michelle Yim at the Tropicana, Christmas 1982, tape 2, CCTV labeled "B048", cuid2022 (Box 137, Betamax Video 759)
  - Video 760: Cinevue Presents Arnie Wong, 3/9/86, cuid2023 (Box 137, Betamax Video 760)
  - Video 761:Workshop Dinner, 10/83: 1st part drama, 2nd part dinner, cuid2024 (Box 137, Betamax Video 761)
  - Video 762: P.S. Henry Street Grade 2 Students Nutrition Show, cuid2025 (Box 137, Betamax Video 762)
  - Video 763: Voting Machine demonstration, 11/5/84, camera original, cuid2026 (Box 137, Betamax Video 763)
  - Video 764: Canadians of Chinese Heritage history, CCTV labeled "B121", cuid2027 (Box 137, Betamax Video 764)
  - Video 765: Chinese Exodus from Vietnam I, CCTV labeled "B21", cuid2028 (Box 137, Betamax Video 765)
  - Video 766: Two Comedians, Interior, tape C, continuous L.S., cuid2029 (Box 137, Betamax Video 766)
  - Video 767: Two Comedians, Interior, tape B, continuous L.S., cuid2030 (Box 137, Betamax Video 767)
  - Video 768: Philip and Henry, CCTV labeled "B43", cuid2031 (Box 137, Betamax Video 768)
  - Video 769: Philip Kon Golanda, CCTV labeled "B77", cuid2032 (Box 137, Betamax Video 769)
  - Video 770: Peter, Paul, Mary, CCTV labeled "B149", cuid2033 (Box 137, Betamax Video 770)
  - Video 771: Jacob, cuid2034 (Box 137, Betamax Video 771)
  - Video 772: Jane Fonda, cuid2035 (Box 137, Betamax Video 772)
  - Video 773: Chinese concert, cuid2036 (Box 138)
  - Video 774: Chinese concert, cuid2037 (Box 138)
  - Video 775: Chinese music: 1) pipa, 2) violin, 3) music, 4) singing, 5) flute, cuid2038 (Box 138)
  - Video 776: Chinese Music Ensemble of New York I, CCTV labeled "B051", cuid2039 (Box 138)
  - Video 777: Chinese Music Ensemble of New York II, CCTV labeled "B052", cuid2040 (Box 138)
  - Video 778: Chinese Opera, cuid2041 (Box 138)
  - Video 779: Chinese singers (AC), cuid2042 (Box 138)
  - Video 780: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera I, CCTV labeled "B027", cuid2043 (Box 138)
  - Video 781: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera II, CCTV labeled "B028", cuid2044 (Box 138)
  - Video 782: Kim Lai Wah Cantonese Opera III, CCTV labeled "B029", cuid2045 (Box 138)
  - Video 783: Opera/Parade/Program, cuid2046 (Box 138)
  - Video 784: Peking Opera, CCTV labeled "B104", cuid2047 (Box 138)
  - Video 785: Traditional Chinese music, cuid2048 (Box 138)
  - Video 786: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "B009", cuid2049 (Box 138)
  - Video 787: Asian American Dance Theater, CCTV labeled "B008", cuid2050 (Box 138)
  - Video 788: Asian American Dance Theater (I), 4/22/78, CCTV labeled "B006", cuid2051 (Box 138)
  - Video 789: Asian American Dance Theater (II), 4/22/78, CCTV labeled "B007", cuid2052 (Box 138)
  - Video 790: Asian American Dance Theater, Riverside Dance Concert, April '83, cuid2053 (Box 138)
  - Video 791: Chen and Dancers, H.T. Dance Company, CCTV labeled "B025", cuid2054 (Box 138)
  - Video 792: Chiang Ching Dance Company, I, CCTV labeled "B010", cuid2055 (Box 138)
  - Video 793: Chiang Ching Dance Company, II, CCTV labeled "B011", cuid2056 (Box 138)
  - Video 794:Hsu Shuh Ying Dance Workshop, CCTV labeled "B057", cuid2057 (Box 138)
  - Video 795: Taiko Drums Amy Kato, Chris Komuro (10 minutes), cuid2058 (Box 138)
  - Video 796: Asian American experience: Charlie Chin in concert, 5/22, CCTV labeled "B56", cuid2059 (Box 138)
  - Video 797: Charlie Chin interview, cuid2060 (Box 138)
  - Video 798: Charlie Chin, CCTV labeled "B001", cuid2061 (Box 138)
  - Video 799: Charlie Chin and Joanne, 4/20/78, CCTV labeled "B026", cuid2062 (Box 138)
  - Video 800: Asian American Experience: Charlie Chin concert, 5/22, tape 8, CCTV labeled "B57", cuid2063 (Box 138)
  - Video 801: Asian American Experience: Asian American artists-Zignal rehearsal, 1/30/80, tape 3, cuid2064 (Box 138)
  - Video 802: Asian American Experience: Asian American artists-Zignal rehearsal, 1/30/80, tape 4, cuid2065 (Box 138)
  - Video 803: Asian American culture, tape 6, cuid2066 (Box 138)
  - Video 804: People's Republic of China (PRC) Troupe #1, cuid2067 (Box 138)
  - Video 805: People's Republic of China (PRC) Troupe#2, cuid2068 (Box 138)
  - Video 806: Dangerous Encounters of the First King (1979) by Radio Television Hong Kong, CCTV labeled "B005", cuid2069 (Box 139)
  - Video 807: Loose Pages Bond (1979), Dir. Chris Choy, CCTV labeled "B001", cuid2070 (Box 139)
  - Video 808: The New Wife (1968), cuid2071 (Box 139)
  - Video 809: Regret for the Past, tape 1, CCTV labeled "B007", cuid2072 (Box 139)
  - Video 810: Regret for the Past, tape II, CCTV labeled "B008", cuid2073 (Box 139)
  - Video 811: Rickshaw Boy (1980), CCTV labeled "B017", cuid2074 (Box 139)
  - Video 812: Teahouse (1982), CCTV labeled "B016", cuid2075 (Box 139)
  - Video 813: Wild Children (1977) by Radio Television Hong Kong, CCTV labeled "B004", cuid2076 (Box 139)
  - Video 814: Willful Murder (1981), CCTV labeled "B014", cuid2077 (Box 139)
  - Video 815: An American Story, Part I, CCTV labeled "B004, cuid2078 (Box 139)
  - Video 816: An American Story, Part II, CCTV labeled "B005, cuid2079 (Box 139)
  - Video 817: And the Soul Shall Dance, CCTV labeled "B018", cuid2080 (Box 139)
  - Video 818: And the Soul Shall Dance, CCTV labeled "B019", cuid2081 (Box 139)
  - Video 819: Arakawa, Manilatown Lives (1986), The Year of the Ox (1973), Snipers in the Trees (1985), cuid2082 (Box 139)
  - Video 820: Boat People, CCTV labeled "B012", cuid2083 (Box 139)
  - Video 821: Bullet Headed Bird II, CCTV labeled "B102", cuid2084 (Box 139)
  - Video 822: Butterfly Love #1, CCTV labeled "B015", cuid2085 (Box 139)
  - Video 823: Butterfly Love #2, CCTV labeled "B016", cuid2086 (Box 139)
  - Video 824:Cross Street, CCTV labeled "0B015", cuid2087 (Box 139)
  - Video 825: Diary of an Amerasian, CCTV labeled "B55", cuid2088 (Box 139)
  - Video 826: Dupont Guy Second Campaign, CCTV labeled "0B002", cuid2089 (Box 139)
  - Video 827: 88 Keys to Revolution, cuid2090 (Box 139)
  - Video 828: Farewell to Manzanar (1976), Part 1, cuid2091 (Box 139)
  - Video 829: The Forgotten Pioneers, CCTV labeled "B122", cuid2092 (Box 139)
  - Video 830: From Mao to Mozart (BI), CCTV labeled "B009", cuid2093 (Box 139)
  - Video 831: If I Were Real, CCTV labeled "B013", cuid2094 (Box 139)
  - Video 832: Kamla (1984), Dir. J. Mundhra, cuid2095 (Box 139)
  - Video 833: No Choice, cuid2096 (Box 139)
  - Video 834: On Culture (Floating Foundation), 2/29/79, tape 1, cuid2097 (Box 139)
  - Video 835: Our Corner (1981) by Beijing Film Institute, CCTV labeled "0B021", cuid2098 (Box 139)
  - Video 836: Return from Silence, by C. W. Shih, CCTV labeled "0B003", cuid2099 (Box 139)
  - Video 837: The Saga of Anatahan (1976), Dir. Josef Von Sternberg, cuid2100 (Box 139)
  - Video 838: Search at the Academy, CCTV labeled "B055", cuid2101 (Box 139)
  - Video 839: Search at the Academy I, CCTV labeled "B053", cuid2102 (Box 139)
  - Video 840: Search at the Academy II, CCTV labeled "B054", cuid2103 (Box 139)
  - Video 841: The Shanghai Story (1954), CCTV labeled "B51", cuid2104 (Box 139)
  - Video 842: Servant of Two Masters Part I, CCTV labeled "B017", cuid2105 (Box 139)
  - Video 843: "Speck in the Water," tape 1, cuid2106 (Box 139)
  - Video 844: "Speck in the Water," tape 2, cuid2107 (Box 139)
  - Video 845: ThailandNot Taiwan, cuid2108 (Box 139)
  - Video 846: Voices of People, CCTV labeled "B020", cuid2109 (Box 139)
  - Video 847: Animation: Animal Olympics, CCTV labeled "B30", cuid2110 (Box 139)
  - Video 848: Bruce Lee: The Legend (NTSC), CCTV labeled "1209", cuid2111 (Box 139)
  - Video 849: Days of Wine and Roses, CCTV labeled "B109", cuid2112 (Box 139)
  - Video 850: Incredible Hulk, CCTV labeled "B6," "B004", cuid2113 (Box 139)
  - Video 851: Lady Sings the Blues, cuid2114 (Box 139)
  - Video 852: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2115 (Box 140)
  - Video 853: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2116 (Box 140)
  - Video 854: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2117 (Box 140)
  - Video 855: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2118 (Box 140)
  - Video 856: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2119 (Box 140)
  - Video 857: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2120 (Box 140)
  - Video 858: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2121 (Box 140)
  - Video 859: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2122 (Box 140)
  - Video 860: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2123 (Box 140)
  - Video 861: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2124 (Box 140)
  - Video 862: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), cuid2125 (Box 140)
  - Video 863: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), translated title: Heavenly messenger of the streets, cuid2126 (Box 140)
  - Video 864: Unidentified, CCTV labeled: (Chinese), translated title: Heavenly messenger of the streets, cuid2127 (Box 140)
  - Video 865: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B36", cuid2128 (Box 140)
  - Video 866: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B42", cuid2129 (Box 140)
  - Video 867: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B74", cuid2130 (Box 140)
  - Video 868: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B98", cuid2131 (Box 140)
  - Video 869: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B99", cuid2132 (Box 140)
  - Video 870: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B110", cuid2133 (Box 140)
  - Video 871: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B129", cuid2134 (Box 140)
  - Video 872: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B131", cuid2135 (Box 140)
  - Video 873: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B134", cuid2136 (Box 140)
  - Video 874: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B145", cuid2137 (Box 140)
  - Video 875: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "B148", cuid2138 (Box 140)
  - Video 876: Unidentified, cuid2139 (Box 140)
  - Video 877: Unidentified, cuid2140 (Box 140)
  - Video 878: Unidentified, cuid2141 (Box 140)
  - Video 879: Unidentified, CCTV labeled "A-17", cuid2142 (Box 141)
  - Video 880: Firing Line: Pornography Debate, CCTV labeled "A-18", cuid2143 (Box 141)